[DIALOGUE]🗣 Bye.
[EPIC]⚡ I didn't come out of.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Hey everybody!
[DIALOGUE]🗣 the light.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Whatever.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 yourself.
[HAPPY]😊 Thank you.
[EPIC]⚡ Thank you.
[EPIC]⚡ Never ever.
[EPIC]⚡ problem.
[EPIC]⚡ was in that view.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 All is not
[DIALOGUE]🗣 drop my core.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 ever confused the car first.
[EPIC]⚡ Thank you.
[EPIC]⚡ Well, when I drive my body...
[EPIC]⚡ Why did you confuse me for my body?
[EPIC]⚡ It's mine.
[EPIC]⚡ me
[DIALOGUE]🗣 down so your bodies are just cars that we operate and drive around.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 the dealership we cost society to set it to label mine.
[EPIC]⚡ yours the Irish oh white
[EPIC]⚡ No money down 0% APR.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 head strike. We're not forced.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 course for the rest of our lives.
[EPIC]⚡ but I fail to see the logic or pride.
[EPIC]⚡ defining myself.
[EPIC]⚡ judge in another by the cars we drive.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 of who we truly are.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 It's found inside.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Listen, I'm not here to tell you how science is conclu-
[EPIC]⚡ We're all making.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Great than the human species, doesn't exist.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Whoever his story is.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Ready?
[DIALOGUE]🗣 the 15th century.
[EPIC]⚡ It has worked perfectly, no.
[EPIC]⚡ and I'll hit a leg.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 one at hand.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Thank you.
[EPIC]⚡ Have a great day.
[EPIC]⚡ gave you.
[EPIC]⚡ Thank you.
[EPIC]⚡ black.
[EPIC]⚡ Asian Native American Middle
[EPIC]⚡ No.
[EPIC]⚡ together.
[EPIC]⚡ no longer living in the...
[EPIC]⚡ calling human beings.
[EPIC]⚡ Ever blind us from seeing a person for who they are.
[EPIC]⚡ instead of saying them from the judge.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Oh, pretty tissue, artificial filters on it.
[EPIC]⚡ When you let an artificial label define yourself.
[EPIC]⚡ that my friend who have chosen smallness of a greatness and minimized your self, confide and divided your self from others. And it is an undeniable fact that whether it's division there will be conflict and conflict starts wars, therefore every war has started over labels, it's always us versus them. So the answer to war, racism, sexism, and every other is a myth so simple that every politician has missed it. It's the labels. We must rip them off. Isn't it funny how no baby is born racist? Yet every baby cries when they hear the cries of another. No matter the gender, culture or color, proven the deep down, we were meant to connect and care for each other. That is our mission. And that is not my opinion. That is the truth in the world that has sold us fiction. Please listen, labels only distort our vision, which is why half of those watching this will dismiss it or feel resistance and conflicted, but just remember, So did the counter pillar. Before it broke through its shell and became the magnificent butterfly, well these labels are our shells and we must do the same thing. So we can finally spread our wings. Human beings were not meant to be slapped with labels like groceries and supermarkets. DNA cannot be regulated by the FDA. We were meant to be free and only in the world.
[EPIC]⚡ It moves them all.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 living.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 So smart.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 You can figure out what's there on with each other.
[EPIC]⚡ for who?
[HAPPY]😊 So what can we do in the face of all this madness and cannot what is the solution? We can love.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 trying to control the mind is like trying to flex.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Just make it.